Thunder Bolt!
I just need to take these
cockatrice feathers back,
and the quest is complete.
Kramen said this would
take at least a week,
but this was an easy day trip.
Shiek! It's me!
Huh?
Captain?!
Hey. You seem well.
Wow, Captain, it's you!
I thought you were an adventurer
out hunting demons!
Captain?!
You're alive.
Happiness, Duke.
Good to see you're okay, too.
Captain!
Yes?!
Where have you been all this time?!
Miner—
You just up and vanished on us,
and the Demon King was defeated!
We've been so worried!
I had a reason for—
And you look like a human now!
Where are your horn and wings?!
I'll tell you, okay?! Just calm down!
Duke's been super worried
since you disappeared.
You didn't need to tell him that!
Captain, explain.
Oh...
Your captain, Yoki,
confessed his love to the
priestess of the hero's party...
and got rejected.
So now I'm living as a human adventurer.
A demon...
...captain...
...as a human?
I live as Yoki the human now.
You guys should live as
you please, too. Okay?
Nope.
Huh?
No.
I don't want that, either.
We're sticking with you.
We want to meet the human
you fell for, anyway.
That'll never work. This is
the human world, remember?
You'd have to hide your true forms.
If you can do it, so can we.
It'll be fine!
Easy.
Well, if you insist...
I hope you three are prepared
for what's to come!
You are absolute scum.
How could you do such a thing to a girl?
Even if it's to give her a human disguise,
taking a harpy's wings away is awful!
You're absolutely right! I was stupid!
Think about what you've done!
She's nice.
You've said that you are
Yoki's former subordinates,
but you don't look like demons.
Wait up!
It's true. I'm a dullahan,
Happiness is a harpy,
and Shiek is a pixie.
I'd take off my head and show you,
but my armor and helmet
are fused together.
Really?
Duke! You've being too
chatty for a dullahan!
You barely spoke at all before!
That's because of you, Captain.
Huh?
I actually hated the captain at first.
Why is that?
He was famous for being a shut-in.
Even when his superior officer, Zaekill,
ordered him to go out and kill humans...
You'd best leave this room...
before I lose myself!
Zaekill said that talking
to Yoki was exhausting,
so he just left him to his
own devices after that.
But that's unacceptable for a demon,
so I tried to correct
the captain by force.
But he turned the tables on me,
gave me all of these ideas...
and that made me who I am today.
You seem to care deeply for him now.
I don't deny that.
Happiness and Shiek, too... Huh?
Where'd they go?
I hope they didn't head for the mansion...
Those fools! Don't they know they'll be
in trouble if anyone other than Cecilia
finds out what they are?!
Happiness! Shiek!
Where did you go?
Shiek...
Oh, do you know this boy, Yoki?
He's, uh... my friend.
I see.
I'm sorry. He didn't cause
any trouble, did he?
Not at all. I love children.
He was running around in the
garden earlier, so I joined him,
but he wore himself out and fell asleep.
Mother, did you see a girl with Shiek?
Oh, yes, I did.
Sophia took her to the house.
Huh?!
Hmm... You have a knack for this.
Remember that angle.
Understood.
Sophia!
Milady and Master Yoki.
This is our new maid, Happiness.
Please treat her well.
Pleasure.
Happiness! Why are you a maid?!
Sophia, this girl is Yoki's friend!
You are?
Truth.
I am very sorry.
I assumed she was a new
hire who started today.
No, I'm sorry for the confusion.
Happiness, go on and get changed.
No.
Huh?
I want to work.
You want to be a maid?!
You haven't been shown to the
servants' quarters yet, have you?
Well, do your best, Happiness.
You're so lucky! You get to
live in this big mansion!
Hard work.
Come visit us again anytime!
Yay! I want some more
of Sophia's sweet tea!
Yoki.
Yes?
I am so glad you liked it.
In addition to her work as a priestess,
she is involved with
some very important people,
being in the hero's party,
and hasn't had much rest of late.
I'm going to make sure she
has the day off tomorrow.
I'd like you to take her
out to have some fun.
Huh?!
This is basically a parent-approved
date, isn't it?
Yoki! I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
She's wearing different
clothes than usual!
They look great!
Yoki?
Oh, er... those glasses...
look nice on you.
It's a disguise.
If I'm recognized as a member of the
hero's party, things will get hectic.
I get it.
It's tough being famous, huh?
I'm sorry you had to go along with this.
Not at all!
I'll work with you to make
today a nice day off!
Well, I'll get my hopes up, then!
They have a new cake, Yoki!
Look at that!
There are so many cute cakes!
Let's stop here for tea later!
Sure.
They're beautiful!
You're the beautiful one!
Meow!
Isn't it cute?
Yes! Super cute!
Yoki?
What do you think?
Amazing!
Thanks to you, I feel like my day-to-day
exhaustion is melting away!
Really?
Yes!
Hell yeah!
Accessories, huh?
Want to go in?
I do!
Isn't that... Cecilia?
Hey! Ceci—
Yuga, you idiot! If you yell out her
name, everyone will know who she is!
Hero! Mikana!
Sorry about that!
So, what brings you here?
We took a day off for the first time
in ages to go out and have fun.
Why don't you join us, Cecilia?
Uh, hello? What, he can't even see me?
I'm sorry, but I'm with
a friend today, so...
A friend?
Have we met somewhere before?
M-Maybe it's just your imagination?
Well, whatever. He can come with us!
You were about to go in this
store, right? So let's go!
Um...
Hey!
For crying out loud... My first date with
Yuga in ages, and this had to happen?
And you, the civilian with the dull face.
What?!
I hope things work out for
you and the priestess.
Huh?!
You were on a date, too, right?
Well, that's how I saw it, at least.
Best of luck to you.
If it works out between you two,
maybe Yuga will give up on her.
R-Right...
Maybe she's actually an okay person.
I wouldn't expect too much with
a dull face like yours, though.
Nope! She's a terrible person!
I heard Cecilia turned down
the hero's marriage proposal.
You did bring your wallet, didn't you?
So he's still interested in her?
I won't lose to the hero just
'cause he's a pretty boy!
Did you find one you like?
Yoki! I'm sorry I left you out there.
Since we're here, I'll buy you a gift.
What? But... are you sure?
Sure, I'm sure. It's to
thank you for last time.
Well, then, I'll take you up on that.
Good idea! I'll pick something
out for Mikana and Cecilia, too!
Hmm, what should I get?
Is he trying to compete with me?
Cecilia.
Yes?
This might be nice.
How pretty.
I think it's wonderful.
Cecilia! How do you like this
hair accessory I picked out?
It's the most expensive
thing in the store!
More expensive doesn't always mean better.
Here, I'll put it on you!
Hey!
You idiot!
Hey, isn't that Lady Cecilia?
And that guy next to her is the hero!
Lady Mikana is with them, too!
And... who is that guy?
Hero!
Lady Cecilia!
Lady Mikana!
Yuga, you idiot!
Let's get out of this
store for the moment!
Damn it...
I have to find Cecilia, quick!
Sir Raven!
I feel like I've seen that
good-looking guy before...
You don't know him? He's the former
swordsman of the hero's party
who was promoted to knight
captain! That's Sir Raven!
Oh, the silent swordsman, huh?
Looks like he's struggling, too.
Hey, look! The hero's over there!
The hero?!
Hey! Now's your chance to run!
This is probably far enough.
Not a word of thanks, huh?
Well, see ya. Wear a disguise
next time you're walking around.
W-Wait!
Huh?
That voice I just heard...
Wait, is that why you
can't talk around people?
Yes. You're... not going
to make fun of me?
I don't... sound very manly, do I?
Everyone has a part of them that
they don't want people pointing out.
Like the fact that I'm a demon.
You're an unusual guy.
Most people laugh at me.
I'm not gonna laugh. Or,
what, do you want me to?
No.
Well, I should be going.
W-Wait!
Um... would you... uh...
b-be my friend?
Huh?
I mean... you don't have
to if you don't want to.
But... the only people who didn't laugh
at my voice were my mom and cousin, so...
Sure. I'm Yoki. Good to know ya.
Really? Thank you! I'm Raven.
I'm glad to know you, too.
Oh, crap! I don't have
time to hang around here!
Sorry! See you later!
Sure...
Where did Cecilia go?
This was our first date, too...
Did Yoki already go home?
It hurts!
Mommy!
What's the matter?
Let's fix whatever hurts first, okay?
Was your mother here with you?
She's gone.
I-It's all right!
Stop crying, young child!
Hup!
I, Yoki, the great adventurer,
will search high and low
until I find your mother!
Yoki!
Yes?!
What in the world are you doing?!
Oh, I'm not a chuuni or anything...
It's just something I
do for kids, you know?
You got in trouble!
We're looking for this boy's mother!
Is this boy's mother in the area?
Hey, Cecilia, maybe you
should head home first.
If you draw too much attention again...
It's all right.
We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
Is this boy's mother around here?
Mommy!
Where is Cecilia?
Yuga, let's just go already.
It'll be chaos if we get caught again.
The priestess is probably
back home by now, too.
There you go again!
Unlike you, I'm worried about Cecilia!
What's his problem?
I found her, Mikana!
Mikana?
THE NEXT DAY
Cecilia collapsed?!
Yes. On top of the exhaustion
she deals with every day,
it seems the commotion yesterday
pushed her over her limit.
Oh, no... This is my fault!
It's just a mild cold.
It's not your fault at all.
The hero, on the other hand...
After he dragged Cecilia
into all that chaos,
he insisted on taking care of her.
I don't even know how he found out.
Ah...
Sophia intercepted him and
managed to send him away.
Right?
Yes. We can't have him making
a fuss around the young lady.
Just what is Sophia, exactly?!
Cecilia told me how much you did for her.
Won't you go and see her?
Milady, Master Yoki is here to see you.
What?! Y-Yoki?! G-G-Give me just a moment!
Don't open the door yet!
No need to worry. I put
your teddy bear away.
Sophia!
Please, go on in.
Here I am...
This is... Cecilia's room?
Yoki?
I'm sorry I look like this.
No, I'm sorry.
It was supposed to be a day off for you.
It wasn't your fault.
No, I knew you were exhausted.
I was wrong to drag you all
over the place like that.
Very well. We'll say it was your fault.
My day off went to waste because of you.
So...
go out with me on my next day off, okay?
Was that... a promise
to go on another date?!
Just leave it to me!
I failed yesterday, but
it will not happen again!
Indulge in all the rest you need
within your colorful cocoon,
and dream of the day you recover
while letting your hopes
swell for our next outing!
Sorry...
A-A-Are you okay, Cecilia?!
Please do not yell. You will
worsen milady's condition.
Okay, well, take care, Cecilia!
Y-Yoki!
Thank you for visiting us today.
I'm sorry...
Captain, you're powerless.
Shut up!
Man, she's unbelievably strong.
Raven?
Yoki? What are you doing here?
Celia asked me to come. What about you?
Um...
Oh, if you'd rather not say, it's fine.
No...
Could I ask for your advice?
Sure, if I can help.
Um, the thing is... there's
someone I'm... interested in.
Wha?!
I wasn't expecting him
to ask for love advice!
I told you I'm not very
confident in my voice, right?
Yeah.
Well, she didn't make fun of me.
She said, "It's a nice voice. I envy you."
Hey, she sounds nice.
Yes, she really is!
And that's why you fell for her, huh?
What should I do?
I'm not confident that I could...
He's like a middle schooler
just hitting puberty.
And he's so good-looking, too.
Raven!
Do you not know yourself at all?!
You've got a nice face, you're tall,
and on top of that, you're a member of
the hero's party that saved the world!
And if she's already complimented your
voice, you have nothing to worry about!
You are awesome! Make a move!
I know you can do it!
Believe in yourself!
Crap! I went into chuuni mode again!
Yeah... You're right.
Thanks. You helped me find my courage.
I'll tell her how I feel.
Good. Go get 'er.
Okay, here I go.
What's Raven doing here, anyway?
Wait, don't tell me the
girl he likes is...
Cecilia?!